AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- School's principle with her guests. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref474)
  Arabic Writing; Food; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Libraries; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Primary school students in class. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref475)
  Boys; Classrooms; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- School event. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref476)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Principle handing out awards to students. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref477)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Trophies
- Teacher with his student during a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref478)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Family Portraits; Fathers; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Mothers; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Party guests at a school event. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref479)
  Arabic Writing; Drinking; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education
- Party guests at a school event. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref480)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education
- Party guests with students at a school event. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref481)
  Arabic Writing; Awards; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education; Students
- Vatican ambassador giving out his speech while a teacher translates. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref482)
  Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Priests; Speech; Teachers
- Group photo of priests with a teacher at a school event. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref483)
  Arabic Writing; Eating; Helwan, Egypt; Libraries; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Crosses; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Group photo of two women and two men. 10.2 x 15.1 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref484)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Women's Clothing
- Teacher/priest speaking into microphone during school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref485)
  Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Speech; Women; Women's Clothing
- School event. 9 x 11.7 cm, 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref486)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Women; Women's Clothing
- Priest holding a boy at school. 15 x 7.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref487)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education
- A teacher receiving an award from the school principal. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref488)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- Students in the Seuz with a dog. 8.8 x 14.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref489)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Dogs; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Suez, Egypt
- Boy playing with a dog during a trip to the Suez., 9 x 13.9 cm; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref490)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Dogs; Field-trip; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Suez, Egypt
- Photo of a terrace on Mansour Street. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref491)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Hotel Evergreen. 7.2 x 10.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref492)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Photographic Prints
- Group photo of scouting pioneers. 12.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref493)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Scouts; Uniforms
- A group of teachers with students. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 26/2/1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref494)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- Khesro Street. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref495)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Carriages/Coaches; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Women; Women's Clothing
- Priest with students. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref496)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Students
- Photo of a terrace on Mansour Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref497)
- Picture of a teacher chatting with a priest and the Vatican ambassador. 8.8 x 11.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref498)
  Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Teachers
- Son of the teacher beside him receiving an award for academic and sports achievement. 10.1 x 15 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref499)
  Academic achievement; Arabic Writing; Awards; Boys; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Student receiving an award. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 26/2/1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref500)
  Awards; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Students with their priest. 13.1 x 18 cm, 1962/63; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref501)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Front view of a museum. 10.2 x 15.3 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref502)
  Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Museums; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait of students with their teachers. 13.1 x 18 cm, 1962/63; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref503)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Students; Teachers
- View of students lining up in a queue from above. 11.9 x 17.9 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref504)
  Architecture; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- View of students lining up in a queue from above. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref505)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- School photo. 11.6 x 16.7 cm, 1966; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref506)
  Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 11.6 x 16.7 cm, 1966; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref507)
- Sixth grade school photo. 12.7 x 18 cm, 1982/83; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref508)
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref509)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- View of students lining up in a queue from above. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref510)
  Architecture; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- Group photo of teachers. 10.8 x 18.1 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref511)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Students behind the school fence. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref512)
  Fences; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Priest/teacher handing out trophies to students. 12.9 x 18 cm, 1962/63; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref513)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trophies
- School photo. 12.7 x 18 cm, 1983/84; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref514)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- Villa Aquilina on Ragheb Street. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref515)
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.3 cm, 1977/78; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref516)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 12.6 x 17.5 cm, 1977/78; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref517)
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref518)
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, 1977; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref519)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.2 cm, 1977/78; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref520)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1969/1970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref521)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref522)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Sixth grade school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref523)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Kindergarten school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref524)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Men; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref525)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 12 x 17.7 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref526)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Pre-school school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref527)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- First grade school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref528)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 11.4 x 15.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref529)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 11.6 x 16.8 cm, 1969/70; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref530)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 11.4 x 16.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref531)
- School photo. 12.6 x 17.7 cm, 1977; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref532)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1977; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref533)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Scouts school photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref534)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Scouts; Students; Teachers; Uniforms
- 12th grade school portrait. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref535)
  Adolescents; Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo of teachers. 12 x 17.8 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref536)
- Second grade school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref537)
- School photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref538)
  Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- House on Ragheb Street. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref539)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Street lamps; Streets/Roads
- Eleventh grade school photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref540)
  Adolescents; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- A truck parked on the street. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref541)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trucks
- Entrance of a house. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref542)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints
- Entrance of a house on Mahmoud Khater Street. 14.1 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref543)
  Arabic Writing; Doors; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints
- An ancient Egyptian cemetery at Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref544)
  Arabic Writing; Cemeteries; Death; Helwan, Egypt; History; Men; Photographic Prints
- Entrance of a house. 13 x 9.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref545)
- House on Hussein Kamel Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref546)
- House on Riad Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref547)
- Sacred Family church. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref548)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Windows
- House on Mustafa Fahmi Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref549)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors; Fences; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Trucks
- House on Mahmoud Khater Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref550)
- Picture of a wall. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref551)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Wall
- A well (?) found in Mohammad Sayed Ahmad Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref552)
- House on Heidar Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref553)
- Balcony in Mahmoud Khater Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref554)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Windows
- House on Riad Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref555)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Stairs; Windows
- House on Mansour Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref556)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Al Tawfiki Mosque. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1986; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref557)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Windows
- View of a house from the bottom on Ragheb Street. 9.6 x 13 cm, 1975; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref558)
- Entrance of a house on Latif Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref559)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Lighthouses; Photographic Prints
- Balcony of a house on AbdelRahman Street. 13 x 8.9 cm, 1959/61; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref560)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints
- Muslim graves in a village. 7.4 x 13 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref561)
  Arabic Writing; Cemeteries; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Muslims; Photographic Prints; Trees
- Landscape of a town. 8.9 x 14 cm, 15 May; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref562)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Street 48 Zulfikar, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref563)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Doors; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Plants; Streets/Roads; Trees
- An archbishopric in Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref564)
  Arabic Writing; Bicycles; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses
- College of the Holy Family in Helwan. 13.8 x 9 cm, 1954; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref565)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Helwan public hospital. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref566)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Hospitals; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Public health; Trees
- 26 Street Ibrahim, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm., 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref567)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Street 22 Mohammed Said Ahmed, Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref568)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Stairs; Streets/Roads; Windows
- Isamail Kamel street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref569)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Building on Yousef Street, Helwan. 9 x14 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref570)
  Arabic Writing; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Construction; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Window Blinds; Windows
- Ain Helwan, sulfur baths. 9 x 13.8, 1888; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref571)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Springs; Statues; Trees
- Helwan public hospital. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref572)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Hospitals; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Public health; Trees
- Truck in front of building on 17 Street Raghab, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref573)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Fences; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Trucks
- College of the Holy Family. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref574)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Trees; Windows
- Grand Hotel, Helwan. 8.9 x 13 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref575)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Trees; Window Blinds
- Street 28 Raghab, Helwan 14 x 9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref576)